[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Chiara and her group will be traveling from Prague
to meet with the Castellanis.
He can't realize that his phone is missing.
So you better be on your way,
or we'll lose our chance to get La Fornarina.
Just tell me which direction he's going.
I hope your wish is that everything goes smoothly tomorrow.
The background you're seeing behind me
is called Piazza del Popolo.
This will also be Chiara's meeting place with the leader of the Castellani family.
Francesco Castellani.
Why does La Fornarina need
to meet with the Castellani family?
If she gets their support,
then Chiara's hold on power over all the mafias in Europe will strengthen.
So we can ensure that we are getting good intelligence.
We're on the same side.
We both want justice for his death.
I'm not your enemy here.
And believe it or not, I trust you.
But with the recent case of Sianong turning out to be a mole,
an enemy plant,
I need to take any necessary precaution,
just to keep my asset safe.
Even the next generation of their family.
Because honestly,
I'm tired of dealing with them.
I'm just giving them a chance because of you.
They are stubborn,
but they're not unreasonable.
I told you,
it's better to talk things out than to try killing each other.
Come in.
Good evening, sir. You have a visitor.
Good evening, General.
-Good evening, General. -Good evening.
You?
No, sir. It's Sister Tess, sir.
Tess.
Are you avoiding me?
Brother Mikoy!
No, I didn't know it was you.
I thought someone was chasing me.
You? How are you?
How's Mom Tess?
You know her.
She's the strongest of us all.
Even though she's hurting inside, she'd never show it to me.
Sorry, Brother Mikoy.
I didn't mean for this to happen.
I didn't tell anyone that you're my informant.
But I need your help.
So Dad's death won't be for nothing.
Yes, Bro.
I'm sorry, okay?
I don't know if this is urgent based on your agency's protocol.
But as a mother,
when it comes to my son, everything is urgent.
Everything is important.
I understand, Tess.
A parent's concern can come at any hour.
Is this about Mikoy?
Norberto, I just can't shake this feeling.
And I don't have anyone else to talk to who would understand me.
Don't worry.
Agent Alex is with Mikoy.
The best agent in this agency.
You know, I do trust Agent Alex.
And I know you're all doing everything you can
to keep them both safe.
But it's Mikoy I'm worried about.
It's like he's changed.
And I know that you know what I mean.
I know Mikoy is old enough to make his own decisions about his life.
But I still can't shake this feeling.
He even told me
that this would really be his last mission.
But no matter what he says,
I don't believe him.
Because I know that he's doing this out of sadness and anger.
But Norberto,
that's not who my son is.
You know Mikoy.
Every decision he makes
is because of love.
I'm really worried about Mikoy.
And you're right.
A lot has changed in Mikoy's life.
What happened to him was no small thing.
It's like fate itself was playing a cruel joke on him.
But in all my years with this agency,
I've seen how pain, sadness,
and anger can change a person.
But I also believe
that Mikoy needs to go through this.
He needs to face the truth.
Face it?
Even if it puts his life at risk?
Even if it gets him killed?
I wouldn't let that happen, Norberto.
I know that here in this agency,
you're like a parent to all the agents here.
And Mikoy has so much respect for you.
Maybe there's still time to call off the mission?
Maybe Mikoy could just come home to us.
We're just ordinary people, after all.
And this isn't the kind of dangerous life I want for my son.
We want Mikoy to be safe too.
We're doing everything we can to make sure no innocent people get hurt.
Tess,
we're on your side.
You can count on me.
Has Francesco made a move?
Not yet.
Cheers.
What is this? Why does it taste like this?
Keep drinking. You'll get used to it.
You know, don't worry about Francesco anymore.
He has nowhere else to go.
I've hacked the CCTV around the hotel,
so we'll have eyes on every movement in and out.
I didn't know
you were this techy.
I guess it's one of the things Agent Sianong taught me
and passed on to me.
But…
You know what's been bothering me?
What was actually real about everything he showed us?
Was he just pretending all this time?
You might be forgetting
that I pretended to be someone else to Chiara too.
Just because we lied about one thing
doesn't mean everything we showed everyone about ourselves was a lie.
For example,
Even though those seven habits didn't believe in him.
Right?
You're right.
Of all people,
you're the one who knows Agent Sianong more.
But I would like to say
that I understand him more.
Why?
Are you also a Lord of the Rings fan?
That's not it.
I thought it was.
Then what?
Because in other areas of life,
we're exactly the same.
We both fell in love.
We both love someone who is in love with someone else.
No, no, you don't have to apologize.
By the way,
I forgot to buy something from the convenience store.
You monitor things for now.
And when you get tired, just let me know.
I'll take over.
Sir, excuse me.
I think your companion already left.
Our companion, Sister Tess?
Yes, sir. She just went out.
Hey.
-They said it was Sister Tess. -Sister Tess?
Wait, hold on, my juice.
Say thanks for the juice.
Keep your voice down. Someone might hear you.
Well, it's your fault!
That bomb you dropped was insane.
What happened?
Nothing. Nothing happened.
Of course.
What did you expect?
That's why I called you, so I could vent.
I don't even know.
I'm such an idiot. I wasn't thinking. I just acted on impulse.
I knew it.
This mission wasn't a good idea.
Your mission there in Italy.
But the agency has no choice because Chiara knows too much.
That's also my struggle, Agent Dara.
And I know this is an unnecessary evil.
But as long as Chiara is alive,
we will not be safe.
I know he won't stop until he gets justice for his father's death.
Sometimes I feel like
this is a government-sanctioned revenge plot for Mikoy.
And for General Norberto,
who was a friend of Sir Mario.
And I find the justification for assassinating Chiara very thin.
Sir, I'm very disappointed that you left me behind here.
I thought it was supposed to be until the end of time.
Please take my daughter.
What happened to the GAGO?
Mikoy.
About what happened yesterday.
Are we really not going to talk about it?
Just forget about it.
I can't just forget about it, Mikoy.
Why?
What I feel for you
makes it complicated.
Why?
Do you think I still love her?
That I still have feelings for her?
Why? You don't anymore?
This isn't Prague.
Even though I am a tifosi.
The Castellani family won't dare do anything stupid here.
Does it matter if I still have feelings for her?
Alex, she killed my father.
She turned her back on me and left me like a fucking idiot.
Will that make my feelings for her disappear?
You know, honestly, I don't know.
But I don't care.
Because all my heart wants right now
is to get justice for what she did to my father.
So tell me, Agent Alex,
that you can do what needs to be done when the time comes.
What is that? A new K-pop group?
I wish it were K-pop.
I will.
La Fornarina.
-They only have one request. -What is that?
Just me, Chiara, and a few bodyguards.
What's happening?
The Castellanis made last-minute changes.
They changed the meeting place for Chiara.
Leave them be for now.
You stay here on the ground, okay?
Okay, take care.
We can't act recklessly.
We haven't scouted the area yet.